http://www.weld-mesh.com/terms-and-conditions

New item added to basket
My Basket
Hide Basket
GabionsShop by CategoryDesign & PricingInformationStandard DesignInstallation InstructionsInstallersRetaining wallsGabion Fencing SystemGabion StoneCustom Size GabionDesign & Pricing Information Standard Design Installation Instructions Gabion Fencing System Gabion Stone Custom Size Gabion Fencing & MeshShop by CategoryWelded MeshMetal Post systemChainlinkSecurity fencingFencing toolsTree GuardsSunshade nettingRabbit nettingRabbit trapsFencing installersOrganic GardensGas Bottle CagesWelded Mesh Metal Post system Chainlink Security fencing Fencing tools Tree Guards Pet Runs & AviariesShop by CategoryBird AviaryDog RunCat RunChicken runPuppy cagesLarge cage for zooBird Aviary Dog Run Cat Run Chicken run Puppy cages CagesShop by CategoryGas bottle cageStandard Security CageCustom Security CagesInstallationSafesMachine GuardingDecorative securitySecurity ScreensGas bottle cage Standard Security Cage Custom Security Cages Installation Safes Insect MeshShop by CategorySoffit vent meshInsect MeshSoffit MeshMosquito meshBeehive FlooringWindow & Door SystemsFly ScreenSoffit vent mesh Insect Mesh Mosquito mesh Beehive Flooring Window & Door Systems Decorative GrillesShop by CategoryCompare GrillesPatterned sheetsRegency diamondHand made interwovenCrimped meshDecorative expandedCar grillesCabinet ManufacturersCane webbingFloor GrillesWooden LatticeCompare Grilles Patterned sheets Regency diamond Hand made interwoven Crimped mesh Wooden Lattice Industrial meshShop by CategoryExpanded MetalChequer PlatePerforated MetalWalkway MeshSecurity LathingWOVEN WIREWOVEN WIRE HOMEExpanded Metal Chequer Plate Perforated Metal Walkway Mesh Security Lathing WOVEN WIRE
Home
Terms and Conditions
Terms and Conditions
CONDITIONS OF SALEAny contract of sale between this company and a customer will be subject to these conditions and the placing of an order with this company shall be deemed to be an acceptance by the customer of these conditions. Any terms or conditions appearing in any document issued by the customer shall have no effect. No variation of any of these conditions shall be binding on this company unless expressly accepted by this company in writing. All photographs, pictures and illustrations shown are for information purposes only. Actual products delivered may vary from those shown but will be in accordance with the specification as described.
PRICEPrices to be charged will be those ruling at the date of the despatch of the material, unless otherwise stated. Prices given in any quotation are those ruling at the date of the quotation and are given for guidance only. All prices are subject to alteration without notice.
DELIVERYThe rate or time of delivery in relation to any consignment or series of consignments is estimated as accurately as possible. This company will do its best to meet the requirements of the customer as to time of delivery as specified in the customer's enquiry but no guarantee or warranty as to time of delivery or rate of deliveries is given or implied. The 24hr delivery option applies to orders placed before 11am. Orders placed after 11am will be shipped on the following day using a 24hr weekday service.
DELIVERIES TO SITESWhere customers request deliveries to sites on or by a specific date, this company will do its best to meet such requirements but the company cannot give any guarantee nor can any claims be accepted on account of late deliveries. This is because our transport service, although normally reliable, is subject to various contingencies beyond our control, including road and weather conditions, breakdowns, accidents, delay in unloading at customer's premises, etc. Furthermore, we are sometimes in the hands of outside transport contractors over whom we do not have direct control. Customers are strongly advised, therefore, not to send labour to sites without first ensuring that the goods have been delivered to the desired location.
DAMAGE OR LOSS IN TRANSITThis company will not accept responsibility for material damage or lost in transit, unless this company and the carriers are notified of the complaint in writing, within three days of the receipt, by the customer of the consignment in respect of which damage or shortage is alleged. And an adequate opportunity is given for inspection of the material in the case of non-delivery of a complete consignment notification must be made in writing within 21 days of the date shown on the advise or delivery note. In any event the liability of this company in respect of material damage or loss in transit, shall be limited to the cost of replacement of the loss or damage material and in the case of damaged goods shall be the subject to such goods being returned to this company at the risk and expense of the customer.
DEFECTIVE MATERIAL(a) This Company shall not be liable to the customer for any consequential or special loss or damage or any loss of profit suffered by the customer by reason of any defect or errors in quality or measurement of goods supplied.(b) Any goods returned to this company by the customer at its own expense within seven days of the receipt, thereof by the customer, and which are found on examination by this company to be defective in quality or measurements. Will be replaced by this company free of charge but that will be the limit of this company's liability.
CUSTOMERS MATERIALIf this company agrees to carry out work on customer's own material, or to store customers' goods after an invoice has been presented for the goods. Such material or goods will be held at the customer's risk and this company will not be responsible for the damage by accident, fire, flood, deterioration or any other cause.
GUARANTEES AND WARRANTIESAny condition warranty guarantee or statement as to the quality of any material or its fitness for any purpose whether express or implied by statute by the common law or by any custom of trade or otherwise is hereby excluded unless given expressly in writing by this company.
CANCELLATION
Your right is to cancel your order starting the moment you place your order and ends 9 working days from the day after you receive your goods.
Confirmation of your cancellation should be sent by email, letter or fax.
This does not apply for custom made goods, (Regency Diamond, Hand made Interwoven grills or any product cut to size)
If you wish to cancel your goods after your order has been shipped, the customer is liable for the return charge.
All goods must be returned within 30 days of notification of cancellation (In their original unused condition). If requesting Fine Mesh Metals to arrange the collection, a working day must be provided where you will be available between 8am and 5pm. If the returned package is not available on the day arranged when the delivery company arrives there will be an aborted delivery charge.
If the customer arranges the return using their own transport the company address is that in the footer of the website.
FORCE MAJEUREIf the manufacture or delivery of any material ordered by the customer, shall be prevented or delayed, directly or indirectly by fire, weather conditions, war (whether formerly declared or not) civil disturbance, strikes, industrial dispute or shortage of materials, or by any other cause outside the complete control of this company. This company shall be entitled to extend the period for the delivery of the materials for such reasonable period as may in the opinion of the company be sufficient to enable the delivery to be made. If this company does so elect, the buyer shall not be entitled to cancel the contract nor to receive any compensation of the resultant delay.
DELIVERY BY INSTALMENTSWhere under the terms of any contract delivery of material to a customer is made by installments whether in accordance with a pre-arranged programme or not the following provisions shall apply.(a) This company shall be entitled, without prejudice to any other right to terminate the contract or to suspend further deliveries there under in any of the following events.(i) If any sum due and payable to this company by the customer is unpaid(ii) If the customer shall without due cause have failed to take delivery of any goods(iii) If the customer has failed to provide any latter of credit bill of exchange or other security required by the contract(iv) If the customer becomes insolvent, or goes into liquidation, whether voluntary or compulsory, (except a voluntary liquidation for the purpose of amalgamation or reconstruction only) or has a Receiver appointed, or if the customer is an individual or a partnership, has entered into any arrangement with his or their creditors or has had a receiving order in bankruptcy made against him or them.(b) No default by this company in respect of any installment shall entitle the customer to determine the contract or to treat it as having been repudiated in regard to any installments remaining to be delivered under the terms of this contract.
PROPERTY TRANSFERProperty in these goods shall only pass to the customer from the date of payment in full, of all sums payable to the company in respect thereof. Until such time the goods remain the absolute property of the company. In default of payment by the customer when lawfully demanded by the company, the company shall be entitled to enter the premises of the customer and recover the goods.
Privacy Policy
What is this Privacy Policy for?
This privacy policy is served by Fine Mesh Metals and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use our websites.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the websites and websites owners. Furthermore the way these websites process, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
The Websites
This websites and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.
Use of Cookies
The websites use cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer / device.
Cookies are small files saved to the user's computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.
This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information [ http://www.google.com/privacy.html ].
Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.
Contact & Communication
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
Email Newsletter
This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.
Subscriptions are taken in compliance with UK Spam Laws detailed in the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003. All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 you may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website's email newsletter program. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the business address at the bottom of this policy.
Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity [this is by no far a comprehensive list]. This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.
In compliance with UK Spam Laws and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 subscribers are given the opportunity to un-subscribe at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign. If an automated un-subscription system is unavailable clear instructions on how to un-subscribe will by detailed instead.
External Links
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
